Clayton Novotney

Software & Data Engineer

I am a Junior at the University of Washington studying Informatics (B.S.) with a focus in data science and information architecture. During the summer of 2018, I attended a 14 week-long coding bootcamp where I learned 3 full stacks of web development and software engineering. While studying at UW, I have been involved with a number of different startups and lab projects where I have developed full stack solutions/products that are currently in use by said start-ups and UW lab researchers.

Experience

Account & Project Manager

Iun 2019 - Mar 2020

Vibe Inc

- Monitored and analyzed customers usage of our product.
- Liaison between customers and product development teams to produce new features available on all hardware.
- Helped customers through email, phone, screen-shares, online presentations and in-person meetings to maximize efficiency with our product.

Full Stack Software Developer

Jun 2018 - Sep 2019

Glimpse Wearables

- Built and deployed various full stack services, including websites, APIs, databases, servers, and the beginning stages of machine learning processes.
- Managed a team of 5 developers responsible for developing, maintaining, and updating previously mentioned services.
- Member of the founding team that helped lead the direction of the company.

Co-founder/Software Developer

Sep 2018 - Present

Ronovo.io

- Cofounded company that builds customer applications and websites for customers interested in expanding online presence and streamlining internal work
- Created custom content for each customer, ranging from logo designs, animations, themes to product images.
- Developed custom software based on customers and businesses needs/specifications.

Alpine Patroller

Apr 2016 - Present

National Ski Patrol

- Completed 10-month Outdoor Emergency Care, CPR and toboggan certifications.
- Mountain patroller that provides customer service to all guests on the mountain, ranging from medical emergencies to conducting search and rescues.

Education

University of Washington

Sep 2016 - Jun 2021

Studying Informatics (B.S.).

Focus in Data Science and Information Architecture.

Member of S.E.A.L Lab.

Co-President of UW Watersports Club.

Coding Dojo

Jun 2018 - Oct 2018
I stacks of web

14 week-long coding bootcamp where I learned 3 full stacks of web development and software engineering. The stacks/frameworks we learned consisted of Python/Django, ASP.Net Core, and MEAN with operational deployment on Amazon Web Services and Microsoft Azure.

Personal Information

Address

5033 21st AVE NE, Seattle WA

Phone

(509) 481-8244

Email

ClaytonNovotney@gmail.com

Github

Github.com/Cnovotn

LinkedIn

LinkedIn.com/in/ClaytonNovotney

Personal Site

Ronovo.io

Coding Languages

Python/Django/Flask

Advanced

SQL/MySQL

Advanced

HTML/CSS/JS/Ajax

Advanced

React/Node.JS

Intermediate

C#/ASP.Net

Intermediate

Go

Intermediate

Java/PHP/R

Beginner

Software Tools

Amazon Web Services

Advanced

Visual Studio Code

Advanced

DataGrip

Advanced

Microsoft Azure

Intermediate

Courses Completed

Information Architecture
Database Design & Management

Intro & Advanced

Server-Side Development

Client-Side Development

Web Programming

Design Methods

Computer Programming, I & II Social Networking Technologies

Technical Foundations